{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Phone System Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39782/":{"taskOID":39782,"originalTaskOID":39782,"setID":314,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3070,"questionDisplayText":"Phone System Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem with the  phone system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1922,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Digital functions aren't working","answerDisplayText":"Digital functions aren't working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4111,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Needs reprogramming","answerDisplayText":"Needs reprogramming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3614,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Line interference","answerDisplayText":"Line interference","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1235,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Can't dial out","answerDisplayText":"Can't dial out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1234,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Can't dial in","answerDisplayText":"Can't dial in","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4198,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No dial tone","answerDisplayText":"No dial tone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2390,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Fast busy signals","answerDisplayText":"Fast busy signals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5773,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Extensions","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many extensions are currently in use?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200814,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fewer than 3","answerDisplayText":"Fewer than 3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200815,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 to 5","answerDisplayText":"3 to 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 to 10","answerDisplayText":"5 to 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200817,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10","answerDisplayText":"More than 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3070,"questionDisplayText":"Phone System Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem with the  phone system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1922,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Digital functions aren't working","answerDisplayText":"Digital functions aren't working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4111,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Needs reprogramming","answerDisplayText":"Needs reprogramming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3614,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Line interference","answerDisplayText":"Line interference","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1235,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Can't dial out","answerDisplayText":"Can't dial out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1234,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Can't dial in","answerDisplayText":"Can't dial in","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4198,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No dial tone","answerDisplayText":"No dial tone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2390,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Fast busy signals","answerDisplayText":"Fast busy signals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1922,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Digital functions aren't working","answerDisplayText":"Digital functions aren't working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4111,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Needs reprogramming","answerDisplayText":"Needs reprogramming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3614,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Line interference","answerDisplayText":"Line interference","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1235,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Can't dial out","answerDisplayText":"Can't dial out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1234,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Can't dial in","answerDisplayText":"Can't dial in","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4198,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No dial tone","answerDisplayText":"No dial tone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2390,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Fast busy signals","answerDisplayText":"Fast busy signals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5773,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Extensions","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many extensions are currently in use?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200814,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fewer than 3","answerDisplayText":"Fewer than 3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200815,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 to 5","answerDisplayText":"3 to 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 to 10","answerDisplayText":"5 to 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200817,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10","answerDisplayText":"More than 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200814,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fewer than 3","answerDisplayText":"Fewer than 3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200815,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 to 5","answerDisplayText":"3 to 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 to 10","answerDisplayText":"5 to 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200817,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10","answerDisplayText":"More than 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/39782/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39782,"taskName":"Telephone System - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Telephone System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Phone System Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1711,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Line Wiring wire Telephone Phone","textMessagingName":"Repr Phone","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically found in an office setting, these systems manage incoming calls, message taking, directories, call routing, transfers, conference calling, on-hold messages \u0026 other telephone functions.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes voicemail, paging, routing, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Telephone System .  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Phone System Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Business Telephones","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Telephone System Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Telephone System - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Telephone System Project","urlName":"Telephone-System-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Phone System Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Line,Wiring,wire,Telephone,Phone,jack","emcCategoryOid":-12026,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":314,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}